

LUIGI PINNA

BIO

IT education, graduated in Economics and Business Management and have always been passionate about technology and information technology. I am highly motivated to constantly develop my skills and to grow professionally. I have worked in various fields and held positions of responsibility that have allowed me to develop interpersonal and time management skills and to build a strong propensity for self-improvement.

SOFT SKILL

Team working
Results-oriented
Adaptability
Logical thinking
Problem Solving
Indipendence

CONTATTI



Email: luigipinna3@gmail.com



Phone: 3406852842



LinkedIn: @luigipinna



https://github.com/luigiPinna



https://luigipinna.com



EDUCATION

Junior Full Stack Developer - The Net Value

03/2021 - 11/2021

- Structured programming with the C language.
- Database management, data modelling and SQL.
- Object-oriented programming on the backend:
 Java language and SpringBoot framework.

 Basic knowledge of C# language and DotNet framework.
 Php and Laravel framework.
- Web-oriented development: Javascript, Typescript with Angular
- Markup and style languages: Html, CSS, Bootstrap
- Python
- Mobile: Android dev
- Tools: Postman, Git, GitHub, Trello, Notion

Final Project

Web App in Angular that, on the Frontend side, suggests to the user various movies to watch on the basis of data taken from different APIs (Movie, Weather and Time) and with the implementation of the following CRUD microservices on the Backend side connected to the respective databases:

- user login and registration with SpringBoot and SpringBoot security
- comment management (.NET)
- rating management (Laravel)
- adding movies to user lists (Angular)

Università degli Studi di Cagliari - Facoltà di Scienze Economiche Giuridiche e Politiche

Degree in Economics and Business Management

Subjects of Study: Accounting, Planning and Control, Financial Mathematics, Corporate Finance, Private and Commercial Law,

ITIS M. Giua - Cagliari

Diploma - Computer Science

- Software development
- Web processing (HTML, CSS, basic JavaScript)
- Network and database



PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Backend Developer and RPA Specialist

@ Aevoluta| 02/2022 - present

- RPA and Backend Development with Python
- UiPath Automation Development
- Process Mining

Marketing Techhnician

@ ElleDi | 07/2020 - 12/2020

- Digitalization
- Data analysis and accounting
- Front and back office

Accounting and Budgeting - Intern

@ Lega Navale Italiana | 03/2019 - 07/2019

- Accounting
- Managing financial statement
- Budgeting and corporate finance



COURSES AND CERTIFICATIONS

Advanced Google Analytics | Google (2020) Digital marketing Foundations | Google (2019) English level B2 Driving licence B Nautical Driving licence Lifeguard certification